<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Bianchi Accountants Limited</title>
    <link>/bianchiaccountants/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Bianchi Accountants Limited</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/bianchiaccountants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Consultancy Services</title>
      <link>/bianchiaccountants/services/consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bianchiaccountants/services/consultancy/</guid>
      <description>We offer a wide range of services for stand-alone projects or consultancy services. Et nec ingentem est minus faciunt praecipue posse auctoremque sedes transmittere. Et nec ingentem est minus faciunt praecipue posse auctoremque sedes transmittere.
Our Consultancy Services
These include
Cash Flow Forecasting and Scenario Analysis Forecasting and Budgeting from Turnover to Profit Lines Implementation of Accounting Systems Upgrading Accounting Systems to give up to date and accurate Financial Information Business Planning and Strategic Corporate Planning Business Valuations Business Disposal and Aquisitions Project Management Services Postquam tamen Et nec ingentem est minus faciunt praecipue posse auctoremque sedes transmittere et pedes miratur erat animaeque.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Individuals</title>
      <link>/bianchiaccountants/services/individuals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bianchiaccountants/services/individuals/</guid>
      <description>We offer tailored support to our clients covering the areas you require. Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec. rem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut lan rem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut lan
Individual Accounting title Income Tax Planning Self Assesment Preparation and Submission Dealing with HMRC Accounting and Tax compliance for Employment Earnings, Investment and Property Portfolios Capital Gains Tax Awareness and Compliance Inheritance Tax Planning </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting</title>
      <link>/bianchiaccountants/services/accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bianchiaccountants/services/accounting/</guid>
      <description>Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec.
Ne verba patulosque numen vix libet Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Exit ex huic Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Loquor videt Ardua non igne caelesti coniugis cognovi diversorum Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Employed</title>
      <link>/bianchiaccountants/services/selfemployed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bianchiaccountants/services/selfemployed/</guid>
      <description>We offer tailored support to our clients covering the areas your business require. Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec.
Business Planning Accounting Advice Employment Regulatory Requirement, PAYE and NIC Payroll Management and Reporting Requirements VAT Registration and Returns Management Accounts Financial Analyis - Helping you get the most out of your Financial Information Inheritance Tax Planning </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owner Managed Business and Limited Companies</title>
      <link>/bianchiaccountants/services/ownermanaged/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 -1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bianchiaccountants/services/ownermanaged/</guid>
      <description>We offer tailored support to our clients covering the areas your company require. Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec.
Company Formation Statuatory Accounts Prepartation and Submissions Corporate Tax Advice, Returns, Preparation and Submission Business Planning and Strategic Reviews Accounting Advice Book Keeping Employment Regulatory Requirements, PAYE and NIC Payroll Management and Reporting Requirements VAT Registration and Returns Management Accounts Financial Analysis - Helping you get the most out of your Financial Information Cash Flow Management Individual Accounting and Tax Advice </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/bianchiaccountants/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bianchiaccountants/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Company Growth</title>
      <link>/bianchiaccountants/growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bianchiaccountants/growth/</guid>
      <description>Placeholder text</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
